MADHUSUDHAN

Sr. Graphic Designer / UI Designer, Product Film Editor

Phone: +91 9986929423 E-mail: kr.madhusudhan81@gmail.com Bengaluru - 560057



SUMMARY

Highly creative designer with extensive experience in Print and Digital Media, who conceptualizes design solutions for - Automobile and Construction Industry, Retail sector, FMCG, POS, B2B, In-Sales products and 360 degree solutions. Skilled in variety of Poster, Mailer, Brochures, Leaflets, Invites, Product Spec sheets, Banner, Exhibition stall Art work, Press Ad, Webpage UI design, GIF, Product Shoot, Logo design & Magazines.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Designs for Print & Digital Media
- Corporate designs
- Webpage UI design
- Product Film
- Photoshoot

- Support Marketing
- Quick and Time Management
- Knowledge in both in-house and Ad agency
- Design to Artwork till Print

EXPERIENCE

SR. GRAPHIC DESIGNER

L&T Construction & Mining Machinery - Bengaluru, 2014 Till date

- All In-house Creative few to list spec sheets, mailers, posters, brochures, Press Ads
- Marketing related activities in promoting sales support
- All-rounder designing from Artwork till Print

ART DIRECTOR

DDBMudra Group - Bengaluru, 2012 - 2014

- In-sales design to promote the retail Sales like brand Big Bazaar shopping mall
- Pitching a new client, Poster and press Ads

VISUALIZER

Saatchi & Saatchi - Bengaluru, 2010 - 2012

- Layout designs, posters, Press ads to promote the Bosch and Coats products
- Exhibition stall Design and Art works

ARTIST

Fourth Dimension India PVT. LTD - Bengaluru, 2006 - 2009

- Retail Solution designs for brands Britannia, Coke and GSK
- Complete below the line communication Design and Art works

SOFTWARES

Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Adobe Premiere, CorelDRAW, Knowledge in HTML, CSS & 3ds Max

EDUCATION

(Bachelor of Arts - Mysore University) – Karnataka Computer Science Course – Hassan, Karnataka Graphics & Animation – Arena & MAAC Bengaluru

ADDRESS -

Madhu

No.11, 3rd cross Krishnegowda Layout, Behind Raghavendra People Tree Hospital, Jalahalli Cross, Bengaluru-560057